This kind of hyper-vigilance,
nightmares,
and involuntarily flinching at sudden noises,
these are all
classic symptoms of PTSD,
post-traumatic stress disorder.
Your nervous system
seems to be stuck in a state of high alert,
as if
the danger is still present.
I will go back to China and find Ms. Lin
to take back everything that belongs to Jìmíng.
Ma'am,
are you sure you want to
have this face transplant surgery?
Yes.
Okay.
I want a new identity.
As long as the money is right,
everything is negotiable.
I also need a death certificate
and a law degree from LSE.
You...
Guan Tian,
you shameless woman!
Jiming!
So what I just...
Liu Yaru,
what's wrong with you?
I'm crazy?
She's a liar.
She doesn't love you at all.
- She... - That's enough.
Who I'm with has nothing to do with you.
Please face reality
and stop doing these embarrassing things.
Tiantian.
Jiming.
Jiming, don't go.
Don't leave me.
Now,
please leave.
Are you okay?
Slow down.
Mom,
what happened to Guan Yu?
Oh,
she sprained her ankle.
Let her
stay in the guest room tonight.
Can't walk at all?
Don't go, there's a third cup.
Enough.
Stop now.
Sorry, Mr. Wen.
I'm sorry to cause you trouble.
Maybe I should just rest a bit
and go home.
Alright.
Don't force yourself.
We have plenty of guest rooms.
No trouble at all.
Mom,
Tian got drunk because Liu Yaru forced her to drink.
Besides,
it's so late already.
Alright then.
Take her to the guest room.
Okay.
Thank you, Mr. Wen.
Let's go.
Be careful.
This is your room.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Since you've made your choice,
you have to face these.
Are you sure?
Are you ready?
I can do it.
Xintian,
was
the name you shouted
mine?
Wang Jiming is the eldest son of Chairman Lin.
The chairman has always regretted what happened back then
and hoped to take him back
and let him inherit the Lin Group.
It's you.
Guan Yu.
Mr. Wen.
Did I wake you?
I couldn't sleep well.
I have a bit of a headache.
The alcohol probably hasn't worn off yet.
So I thought I'd
come out to get some fresh air.
I really just can't get used to sleeping in the guest room.
Or
are you looking for something?
I have trouble sleeping in unfamiliar beds.
Attorney Guan
I don't care what your purpose is
getting close to Jiming
or whatever it is you're after
The Lin family's door
isn't something you can just walk through whenever you want
Without my approval
it's all just empty talk
Chairman Wen
I understand your concerns
But between me and Jiming,
it's not what you think,
full of calculations.
As for the door of the Lin family,
the door is opened for people,
and people don't live for the threshold.
What's important is
whether the people behind the door
are united in heart.
Isn't it?
A wife of the Lin family
needs a strong background
and support,
not trouble.
I will prove my worth.
What I can bring to Jiming
far outweighs what he would lose.
I will help him protect the Lin Group.
Value
is the eternal pass.
I hope the value of Guan Law
can withstand
any scrutiny.
Thank you for your advice.
I'll leave you to it.
I'll go back and rest.
Good night, Mr. Wen.
Jiming,
Liu Yaping came to me
before she left yesterday
and asked me about you and Yaru.
I've calmed her down,
But we still
have to make a stance.
In a few days,
you should personally go to the Liu family
to apologize.
And finalize the cooperation details
of the project in the south of the city.
Mom,
I've told you,
Yaru and I...
This is not your personal emotional issue.
It's a business alliance and trust between two families.
The Lin Group is about to go public,
and we need the support of the Liu family
and a clean audit report.
The cost of your caprice
is the interests of the entire group.
Don't be confused
by a momentary
and fleeting temptation.
I'll handle the company's affairs well.
But my marriage
is not a bargaining chip.
Marriage?
Jiming,
you're still too young.
Guan Law Firm,
what do you think?
As lawyers,
you understand the spirit of contracts the most.
What is more important,
passion or
business interests?
Moreover,
some relationships
are not even contracts.
They are just
games between adults.
It's more decent to know
when to quit.
I'm full.
I'll go first.
Mr. Wen,
I'll take my leave.
I'll see you another day.
You were too hasty in your probing that day.
You're an adult.
You should be more composed in handling things.
However,
Guan Tiantian
does have issues.
Here's some information
I had gathered.
Guan Tiantian,
graduated from LSE in the UK.
Her resume
is impressive,
but there's about a year
that's almost blank.
No records of schooling,
employment,
or residence.
Her family background
and social relations
are also vague.
Blank?
Then keep investigating.
Spend whatever it takes.
The focus is on that blank period.
I will never let her be with Jiming.
To be honest,
I really dislike Lin Jiming.
If it weren't for Dad's last wish,
I'd never let you
marry him.
Could you stop targeting him?
He's starting to resent me.
Why are you always siding with him?
He's the one who's targeting me,
not the other way around.
It's you, it's you, it's you!
Enough, enough.
You don't understand
the affairs of the group.
Guan Tian,
leave her to me.
I'll find a way to deal with her
to vent my sister's
anger.
That's more like it.
Hey.
Jiming,
let's talk.
Just five minutes.
I'm busy right now.
There's an emergency meeting
regarding Guan Tiantian.
She must have ulterior motives in approaching you.
I've investigated her.
Her background...
You investigated her?
I did it for your sake
and for the company's.
In her overseas study record,
there's a blank period.
And her background is suspiciously clean.
Also, don't you think
every single case she's handled
seems to be targeting the Lin family?
I don't need you meddling in my affairs.
And I especially don't want
you meddling the way you did last night.
I...
Does your father live here too?
I haven't seen him.
Since my dad had a stroke,
he's been in a sterile room
on the top floor,
and also goes to the hospital regularly.
I rarely see him.
[Where]
[is Lin Muyun hiding?]